commerce_robber_seq_1.1	By handing over things obediently, bloodshed can be avoided.
commerce_robber_seq_1.2	I am the famous poison king Qien. When you meet me, scream happily! Because your business today can be closed in advance. Ah ha ha!!!
commerce_robber_seq_1.3	Next, my attack will bloom like a flower in the narrow road of Guanshan!
commerce_robber_seq_1.4	People on the road over there~ Where are you going to rush with something that looks good in color?
commerce_robber_seq_1.5	I want to... take away the trade goods... and your life!
commerce_robber_seq_1.6	Mine... all mine! Ahahahaha !!!
commerce_robber_seq_1.7	Huhu, don't you think you can escape my eyes?
commerce_robber_seq_1.8	These trade supplies seem to be drooling.
commerce_robber_seq_2.1	Find out the location of the wanted criminal by arresting the looting gang.
commerce_robber_seq_2.2	The looting gang has been repelled
event_mob.1	The leader of the plundering gang: Little ones, take them all to me!
event_mob.2	The leader of the plundering gang: Stop!
event_mob.3	The leader of the plundering gang: stay and buy money!
event_mob_smuggler.1	The leader of the looting gang: Little ones, show him some color!
event_mob_smuggler.2	The leader of the plundering gang: Where do you want to go with the smuggled goods?
event_mob_smuggler.3	The leader of the plundering gang: Good things need to be shared with everyone!
farming_zone1.1	Participated in the battle. Please join forces with your surrounding colleagues to defeat the enemy.
farming_zone1.2	Has been separated from the battle. It is best to find a safe place to avoid it.
farming_zone1_seq_1.1	You can feel violent tremors coming from deep in the woods.
farming_zone1_seq_1.2	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_1.3	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_1.4	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_1.5	The attack has begun!
farming_zone1_seq_2.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_2.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_2.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_2.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone1_seq_3.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_3.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_3.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_3.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone1_seq_4.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_4.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_4.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_4.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone1_seq_5.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_5.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_5.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_5.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone1_seq_6.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_6.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone1_seq_6.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_6.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone1_seq_7.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone1_seq_7.2	The tremor in the depths of the woods became smaller and smaller. There should be no more monster attacks.
farming_zone1_seq_7.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone1_seq_7.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2.1	Participated in the battle. Please join forces with your surrounding colleagues to defeat the enemy.
farming_zone2.2	Has been separated from the battle. It is best to find a safe place to avoid it.
farming_zone2_seq_1.1	You can feel violent tremors coming from deep in the woods.
farming_zone2_seq_1.2	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_1.3	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_1.4	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_1.5	The attack has begun!
farming_zone2_seq_2.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_2.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_2.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_2.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2_seq_3.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_3.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_3.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_3.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2_seq_4.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_4.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_4.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_4.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2_seq_5.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_5.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_5.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_5.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2_seq_6.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_6.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone2_seq_6.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_6.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone2_seq_7.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone2_seq_7.2	The tremor in the depths of the woods became smaller and smaller. There should be no more monster attacks.
farming_zone2_seq_7.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone2_seq_7.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3.1	Participated in the battle. Please join forces with your surrounding colleagues to defeat the enemy.
farming_zone3.2	Has been separated from the battle. It is best to find a safe place to avoid it.
farming_zone3_seq_1.1	You can feel violent tremors coming from deep in the woods.
farming_zone3_seq_1.2	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_1.3	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_1.4	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_1.5	The attack has begun!
farming_zone3_seq_2.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_2.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_2.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_2.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3_seq_3.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_3.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_3.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_3.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3_seq_4.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_4.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_4.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_4.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3_seq_5.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_5.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_5.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_5.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3_seq_6.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_6.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone3_seq_6.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_6.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone3_seq_7.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone3_seq_7.2	The tremor in the depths of the woods became smaller and smaller. There should be no more monster attacks.
farming_zone3_seq_7.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone3_seq_7.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4.1	Participated in the battle. Please join forces with your surrounding colleagues to defeat the enemy.
farming_zone4.2	Has been separated from the battle. It is best to find a safe place to avoid it.
farming_zone4_seq_1.1	You can feel violent tremors coming from deep in the woods.
farming_zone4_seq_1.2	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_1.3	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_1.4	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_1.5	The attack has begun!
farming_zone4_seq_2.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_2.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_2.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_2.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4_seq_3.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_3.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_3.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_3.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4_seq_4.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_4.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_4.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_4.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4_seq_5.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_5.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_5.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_5.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4_seq_6.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_6.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone4_seq_6.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_6.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone4_seq_7.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone4_seq_7.2	The tremor in the depths of the woods became smaller and smaller. There should be no more monster attacks.
farming_zone4_seq_7.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone4_seq_7.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5.1	Participated in the battle. Please join forces with your surrounding colleagues to defeat the enemy.
farming_zone5.2	Has been separated from the battle. It is best to find a safe place to avoid it.
farming_zone5_seq_1.1	You can feel violent tremors coming from deep in the woods.
farming_zone5_seq_1.2	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_1.3	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_1.4	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_1.5	The attack has begun!
farming_zone5_seq_2.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_2.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_2.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_2.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5_seq_3.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_3.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_3.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_3.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5_seq_4.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_4.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_4.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_4.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5_seq_5.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_5.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_5.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_5.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5_seq_6.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_6.2	Although the attack still stopped, the tremor continued.
farming_zone5_seq_6.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_6.4	The attack has begun again!
farming_zone5_seq_7.1	I started to hear something coming here!
farming_zone5_seq_7.2	The tremor in the depths of the woods became smaller and smaller. There should be no more monster attacks.
farming_zone5_seq_7.3	Because the distance from the tree was too far, I could not get the reward.
farming_zone5_seq_7.4	The attack has begun again!
fishing_monster.1	The surroundings are too noisy to concentrate on fishing.
fishing_monster.2	Unable to catch fish due to restlessness.
fishing_monster.3	The surroundings are too noisy to concentrate on fishing.
fishing_monster.4	Unable to catch fish due to restlessness.
fishing_monster_skatha01.1	Something huge jumped up from the water!
fishing_monster_skatha01.2	The enemy is jumping out of the water!
fishing_monster_skatha02.1	The monster jumped out of the water!
fishing_monster_skatha02.2	Something attacked from the water!
fishing_monster_skatha02.3	The enemy is jumping out of the water!
