1	The Runda Server Open event starts.
2	Fantastic Summer experience event.
3	Start the G10 Countdown Experience event.
4	A runa server open event is in progress.
5	Fantastic Summer experience event is in progress.
6	G10 countdown experience event is in progress.
7	The Runda Server open event ends.
8	Fantastic Summer experience event.
9	G10 countdown experience event ends.
10	The Runda Server Open event starts.
11	Fantastic Summer experience event.
12	Start the G10 Countdown Experience event.
13	Starts an exciting experience event.
14	A runa server open event is in progress.
15	Fantastic Summer experience event is in progress.
16	G10 countdown experience event is in progress.
17	Exciting experience event is in progress.
18	The Runda Server open event ends.
19	Fantastic Summer experience event.
20	G10 countdown experience event ends.
21	Ends the exciting experience event.
22	Part-time job double starts.
23	Start the 2x experience event.
24	A part-time job double event is in progress.
25	Double experience is in progress.
26	Part-time job double event ends.
27	Ends the experience 2x event.
28	The 5th anniversary experience event starts.
29	The 5th anniversary experience event is in progress.
30	The 5th anniversary experience event ends.
34	The blessing activity has begun.
35	The blessing activity is ongoing.
36	The blessing event has ended.
37	Chapter 4 Open Event
38	Chapter 4 open event in progress
39	End of Chapter 4 Open Event
40	Double experience, double drop rate, double AP activity started.
41	Double experience, double drop rate, double AP activity is in progress.
42	Double experience, double drop rate, double AP event is over.
43	The Rocky Thanksgiving event has begun.
44	The Rocky Thanksgiving event is underway.
45	The Rocky Thanksgiving event is over.
46	Start a reward event. Reward history: Monster experience (5x)
47	The activity begins. Activity content: monster experience value (10 times)
48	A reward event is in progress. Reward history: Monster experience (5x)
49	The activity is in progress. Activity content: monster experience value (10 times)
50	activity ends.
51	activity ends.
52	Start an event. Event History: Monster experience (5x)
53	The activity begins. Activity content: monster experience value (10 times)
54	The event is in progress. Event History: Monster experience (5x)
55	The activity is in progress. Activity content: monster experience value (10 times)
62	Trade profit doubling activity is underway.
63	The trade profit doubling event is over.
64	The trade profit doubling activity has begun.
82	The event has begun. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (2 times), trade profit (2 times)
83	The event has begun. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (5 times), trade profit (2 times)
84	The event has begun. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (7 times), trade profit (2 times)
85	The event has begun. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (10 times), trade profit (2 times)
86	The activity is in progress. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (2 times), trade profit (2 times)
87	The activity is in progress. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (5 times), trade profit (2 times)
88	The activity is in progress. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (7 times), trade profit (2 times)
89	The activity is in progress. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (10 times), trade profit (2 times)
90	The event is about to end. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (2 times), trade profit (2 times)
91	The event is about to end. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (5 times), trade profit (2 times)
92	The event is about to end. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (7 times), trade profit (2 times)
93	The event is about to end. The content of the event is: monster killing experience (10 times), trade profit (2 times)
94	The 7 times experience activity started. The content of the activity is: Killing monster experience points (7 times)
95	The 7 times experience activity is underway. The content of the activity is: Killing monster experience points (7 times)
96	The 7 times experience event is coming to an end. The content of the activity is: Killing monster experience points (7 times)
100	The activity begins. Activity content: monsters experience value (2 times)
101	The activity is in progress. Activity content: monsters experience value (2 times)
102	activity ends. Activity content: monsters experience value (2 times)
103	The activity begins. Activity content: monsters experience value (3 times)
104	The activity is in progress. Activity content: monsters experience value (3 times)
105	activity ends. Activity content: monsters experience value (3 times)
106	There will be some special situations in the world of Irene: 2 times the combat experience value
107	There will be some special conditions in the world of Irene: the drop rate of the item is 2 times
108	Some special circumstances will happen in the world of Irene: Trade Ducat 2 times
109	There will be some special conditions in the world of Irene: Trade gold coins 2 times
110	There will be some special conditions in the world of Irene: Trade experience value 2 times
111	There will be some special conditions in the world of Irene: Trade experience value 2 times
112	Some special situations are happening in the world of Irene: 2 times the combat experience value
113	Some special situations are happening in the world of Irene: item drop chance is 2 times
114	Some special conditions are happening in the world of Irene: Trade Ducat 2 times
115	Some special conditions are happening in the world of Irene: trade gold coins 2 times
116	Some special situations are happening in the world of Irene: Trade experience value is 2 times
117	Some special situations are happening in the world of Irene: Trade experience value is 2 times
118	The special situation of Erin's world has disappeared: combat experience value is 2 times
119	The special situation of Erin's world has disappeared: the item drop rate is 2 times
120	The special situation of Irene's world has disappeared: Trade Ducat 2 times
121	The special situation of Erin's world has disappeared: trade gold coins twice
122	The special situation of Erin's world has disappeared: trade experience value 2 times
123	The special situation of Erin's world has disappeared: trade experience value 2 times
124	Irene will have some special conditions.: Battle experience points, item drop rate 2 times
125	Some special situations will happen to Irene.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience value
126	Some special situations will happen to Irene.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience value
127	Irene is experiencing some special situations.: Battle experience points, item drop rate 2 times
128	Irene is experiencing some special situations.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience
129	Irene is experiencing some special situations.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience
130	Some special situations that occurred in Irene are over.: Battle experience points, item drop rate 2 times
131	Some special situations that occurred in Irene are over.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience
132	Some special situations that occurred in Irene are over.: Trade Ducats, Gold Coins, 2x experience
139	The new event begins. Activity content: Double the training value of cooking-related skills
140	There are currently activities in progress. Activity content: Double the training value of cooking-related skills
141	activity ends. Activity content: Double the training value of cooking-related skills
142	The activity begins. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (2 times)
145	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (2 times)
148	activity ends. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (2 times)
151	The activity begins. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (5 times)
152	The activity begins. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (10 times)
153	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (5 times)
154	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (10 times)
155	activity ends. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (5 times)
156	activity ends. Activity content: Eating skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (10 times)
157	The activity begins. Activity content: Skill cultivation value related to travel and trade talent (2 times)
158	The activity begins. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (2 times)
159	The activity begins. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (5 times)
160	The activity begins. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (10 times)
161	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skill cultivation value related to travel and trade talent (2 times)
162	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (2 times)
163	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (5 times)
164	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (10 times)
165	activity ends. Activity content: Skill cultivation value related to travel and trade talent (2 times)
166	activity ends. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (2 times)
167	activity ends. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (5 times)
168	activity ends. Activity content: Skills related to travel and trade skills (2 times), monster killing experience (10 times)
208	The treasure hunter event has officially started. Activity content: The training value of skills related to travel and treasure hunters (2 times)
209	Start an event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (2x)
210	Start an event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (5x)
211	Start an event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (10x)
212	Activities related to treasure hunters are underway. Activity content: The training value of skills related to travel and treasure hunters (2 times)
213	The event is in progress. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (2x)
214	The event is in progress. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (5x)
215	The event is in progress. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (10x)
216	The treasure hunter activity has ended successfully. Activity content: The training value of skills related to travel and treasure hunters (2 times)
217	End the event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (2x)
218	End the event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (5x)
219	End the event. Event History: Travel talent, Treasure Hunter talent related skill training (2x), monster experience (10x)
220	Start an event. Event History: Drop Gold (2x)
221	The event is in progress. Event History: Drop Gold (2x)
222	End the event.
223	Start an event. Event History: Quest experience (2x)
224	Start an event. Event History: Quest Gold (2x)
225	Start an event. Event History: Drop item (2x)
226	The event is in progress. Event History: Quest experience (2x)
227	The event is in progress. Event History: Quest Gold (2x)
228	The event is in progress. Event History: Drop item (2x)
229	End the event.
230	End the event.
231	End the event.
232	The activity begins. Activity content: Item drop (2 times), combat experience value (5 times)
233	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Item drop (2 times), combat experience value (5 times)
234	activity ends.
235	The special event opens. Activity content: Ninja talent related skills training value (2 times)
236	There are currently special events in progress. Activity content: Ninja talent related skills training value (2 times)
237	The special event has ended successfully. Activity content: Ninja talent related skills training value (2 times)
238	Ronapan Server Open Commemoration Event
239	Lona version server open commemoration event is in progress
240	Ronapan Server Open Celebration Event Ends
241	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only cultivate related skills (double), monster experience (double)
242	Has entered the active period. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double)
243	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine the related skills (double), monster experience (double)
244	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double)
245	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
246	Has entered the active period. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
247	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine related skills (double), monster experience (3 times)
248	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (3 times)
249	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only cultivate related skills (double), monster experience (double)
250	The activity is in progress. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double)
251	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine the related skills (double), monster experience (double)
252	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double)
253	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
254	The activity is in progress. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
255	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine related skills (double), monster experience (3 times)
256	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (3 times)
257	The event period has ended. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only cultivate related skills (double), monster experience (double)
258	The event period has ended. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double)
259	The event period has ended. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine the related skills (double), monster experience (double)
260	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double)
261	The event period has ended. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, and gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
262	The event period has ended. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times)
263	The event period has ended. Activity content: Bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine related skills (double), monster experience (3 times)
264	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (3 times)
265	Has entered the active period. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time experience value (double)
266	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (double), part-time experience (double)
267	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), item drop rate (double)
268	Has entered the active period. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), part-time reward (double)
269	Has entered the active period. Activity content: bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine skills related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), drop gold coins (double)
270	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (3 times), part-time reward (double)
271	Has entered the active period. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time gold coins (double)
272	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double), part-time gold coins (double)
273	Has entered the active period. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double), part-time gold coins (double)
274	The activity is in progress. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time experience value (double)
275	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (double), part-time experience (double)
276	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), item drop rate (double)
277	The activity is in progress. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), part-time reward (double)
278	The activity is in progress. Activity content: bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine skills related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), drop gold coins (double)
279	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (3 times), part-time reward (double)
280	The activity is in progress. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time gold coins (double)
281	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double), part-time gold coins (double)
282	The activity is in progress. Activity content: Skills related to cooks, blacksmiths, tailors, and carpenters (double), monster experience (double), part-time gold coins (double)
283	The event period has ended. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time experience value (double)
284	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (double), part-time experience (double)
285	The event period has ended. Activity content: Warriors, fighters, lancers, magicians, archers, puppeteers, gunners can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), item drop rate (double)
286	The event period has ended. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, and explorer related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), part-time reward (double)
287	The event period has ended. Activity content: bard, battle alchemy, and alchemy to refine skills related skills training value (double), monster experience value (3 times), drop gold coins (double)
288	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (3 times), part-time experience (double)
289	The event period has ended. Activity content: trade, priest, pharmacist, explorer can only related skills training value (double), monster experience value (double), part-time gold coins (double)
290	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (double), part-time experience (double)
291	The event period has ended. Activity content: Skills related to cooking, blacksmith, tailor, and carpentry (double), monster experience (double), part-time experience (double)
292	Has entered the active period. Activity content: combat experience value (5 times), all skills training (double)
293	Currently in active period. Activity content: combat experience value (5 times), all skills training (double)
294	The event period has ended. Activity content: combat experience value (5 times), all skills training (double)
295	Start an event. Event History: All skill training values (10x)
296	The event is in progress. Event History: All skill training values (10x)
297	End the event. Event History: All skill training values (10x)
301	The activity begins. \nActivity content: melee ability related skill training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
302	The activity is in progress. \nActivity content: melee ability related skill training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
303	activity ends. \nActivity content: melee ability related skill training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
304	The activity begins. \nActivity content: Archery skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
305	The activity is in progress. \nActivity content: Archery skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
306	activity ends. \nActivity content: Archery skills related skills training value (2 times), monster killing experience value (3 times)
307	The event starts.\nEvent History: 10 times the item drop rate
308	Start the event.\nEvent History: 10 times AP gain
309	The event starts.\nEvent History: Part-time reward 10 times, trade reward 10 times
310	The event is in progress.\nEvent History: 10 times the item drop rate
311	Event in progress.\nEvent History: 10 times AP gain
312	Event in progress.\nEvent History: Part-time reward 10 times, trade reward 10 times
313	The event ends.\nEvent History: 10 times the item drop rate
314	End the event.\nEvent History: 10 times AP gain
315	The event ends.\nEvent History: Part-time reward 10 times, trade reward 10 times
