1	If you want to dye your hair,\which color would you choose?
2	What is the most important thing to get up in the morning?
3	What do I do first in the morning?
4	If I suddenly have time in the afternoon,\nI want to go to such a place.
5	If I let me choose a superpower\nWhich one of the following would I choose?
6	Which of the following instruments do you want to learn to play most?
7	Which props do you want most in the following projects?
8	Which of the following words are you more interested in?
9	How many times can you breathe in 1 minute?
10	If you can only eat one diet in a month\nWhich of the following would you choose?
11	If there is a cursed book, anyone who reads it will die. \nWhat would you do if you got this book?
12	Which of the following emotions do you have the most unbearable?
13	Which of the following animals do you think you are more similar to?
14	Under the starry sky, when meteors pass by\nYou made a wish, what would that wish be?
15	What is your favorite planet in the solar system?
16	If you go to a bookstore to pick books. \nWhere will you go?
17	If you went to the cafe,\nwhat would you order?
18	If you are invited to a Halloween party! \nWhat would you dress like?
19	If you are hungry and you go to a convenience store, what would you choose?
20	If you choose your favorite holiday from the following options, which one would you choose?
21	You who are thirsty,\nWhich drink would you choose?
22	If you have the opportunity to start playing a new game,\nwhich one of the following options would you choose?
23	When the long holiday is approaching,\nWhich of the following things will you think of first?
24	The fragrance from the other party suddenly rushed to his face. \nWhat kind of taste is this?
25	If the other party suddenly presents a flower to you. \nWhat kind of flower will it be?
26	Dark brown
27	Chocolate brown
28	Orange Brown
29	brown
30	Creamy brown
31	maroon
32	Red Wine
33	Golden brown
34	tan
35	blond
36	Bright blonde
37	Khaki
38	Black hair
39	Blue black
40	Natural brown
41	Sweet orange
42	Pink
43	Just another 10 minutes! Sleep late in the morning
44	It's not okay to be hungry. breakfast
45	It's beautiful anytime! Dignified appearance
46	Must not be missed! Morning news
47	Endure it will get sick! WC.
48	Stretch
49	Close your eyes again
50	Go to the toilet
51	Change clothes
52	Wash your face clean
53	Drink a glass of water
54	Deserted movie theater
55	Quiet big park
56	Quiet library
57	Uninhabited suburbs
58	Winter seaside
59	Noisy street market
60	Shopping paradise, shop
61	I like to stay at home
62	Invisible transparent person
63	The ability to fly in the sky
64	The ability to live forever and die
65	Turn the stone into gold! Hand of Midas
66	The ability to transform into everything
67	Go wherever you want! Teleport
68	咚咚咚 Hawaiian Ukulele
69	Romantic acoustic guitar
70	Dang Dang Dang Dang Drum
71	Huh! electric guitar
72	Heavy bass
73	Handsome, violin
74	Set off the atmosphere, cello
75	Nothing can do it, cymbals
76	Practice hard, trumpet
77	Full of ancient charm, xylophone
78	Endless harmonica
79	Traditional Gayageum
80	Very difficult, Xuan Heqin
81	Very beautiful costume
82	Nice jewelry
83	Very powerful weapon
84	Personalized robe
85	Cosplay costume
86	Powerful armor
87	Dump truck
88	Trampoline
89	America
90	Colorado
91	Spaghetti
92	pressure
93	Yogurt
94	Yakult
95	screwdriver
96	12
97	13
98	14
99	15
100	16
101	17
102	18
103	kimchi
104	mushroom
105	Shallots
106	Bean paste
107	milk
108	Sue cotyledons
109	Anchovy
110	peanut
111	Can't help but look curious
112	Burn immediately
113	Give to others first
114	Keep it until you die
115	Don't watch it, forget it completely afterwards
116	lonely
117	anxiety
118	miss
119	anger
120	despair
121	Sense of nothingness
122	Voles
123	Alpaca
124	zebra
125	tiger
126	owl
127	Koala Bear
128	Vulture
129	frog
130	earthworm
131	Without any wish, disappear quickly!
132	I hope someone will show up
133	Hope to make big money
134	Hope to conquer the world
135	Hope to send a fried chicken takeaway!
136	Let other people's wishes invalidate!
137	Mercury
138	Venus
139	Mars
140	Jupiter
141	Saturn
142	philosophy
143	economics
144	engineering
145	reasoning
146	in love
147	adventure
148	Comics
149	history
150	art
151	theology
152	criticism
153	Cold american coffee
154	Cappuccino full of foam
155	Sweet Fabuccino
156	Sweet and Sour Iced Tea
157	Hot herbal tea
158	Pastel green tea latte
159	Zombies that look a little sick
160	Handsome vampire
161	Lively and cute cupid
162	Majestic great magician
163	Surprise Santa
164	Innocent and poor fairy
165	Put on animal ears and tails
166	Gorgeous party dress
167	Seaweed Rice Ball
168	Coffee milk
169	sandwich
170	Bowl of noodles
171	Puffed biscuits
172	Steamed buns
173	Oden, barbecue stick
174	Chinese New Year
175	Dragon Boat Festival
176	New Year's Eve
177	Korean food
178	Carbonated drinks
179	Cup of hot coffee
180	Ordinary mineral water
181	Refreshing juice
182	Scented herbal tea
183	A tense shooting game
184	Another me, RPG
185	Fighting instinct, fighting game
186	Scary horror game
187	Heartbeat memories, love formation
188	Highway stalls
189	Someone's gift
190	Pocket money coming and going
191	With friends
192	Watch the long holiday special
193	Nagging from relatives
194	Delicious holiday diet
195	Aroma fruity
196	Nice floral fragrance
197	The smell of shampoo and soap
198	No taste
199	Some kind of fragrant smell
200	Daffodil
201	Rose flower
202	Gypsophila
203	lily
204	Half branch lotus
205	Dahlia
206	Hundred Days Red
207	Calendula
208	Morning glory
209	Hibiscus
210	daisy
