5	Women first
9	No killing
21	No! Life Potion
22	No! Stamina Potion
23	No! Magic Potion
24	Quickly restore potion allergies
25	Kid is my friend
26	Guardian of nature
27	The first step towards the rich
38	Health is the most important
39	Our family can go around the dungeon a hundred times even if we don't take the potion of life.
40	The physical strength of our family is the highest for Irene.
41	The weapons used by our family are knives and bows, no magic is needed!
42	Our family is allergic to the quick recovery potion and the body does not absorb it. Let's use other ones.
43	Losing weight too much will hurt the body, chubby is best, \nIt is forbidden to eat wild fruits to lose weight.
44	Our family has a very thorough understanding of the spirit of chivalry, and calls for protection of women both inside and outside the family. (Don't fight female monsters casually!)
45	Our family protects Irene’s baby, the kid, and the people who beat the kid are bad guys.
46	Our family is the guardian of nature and will not hunt animals at will.
47	The goal of our family is to be rich, and the first step to be rich is not to throw away even small things.
48	Our family loves all lives, let us do good and cherish all lives together.
