0	xml.supportpuppet.0
1	xml.supportpuppet.1
2	xml.supportpuppet.2
3	xml.supportpuppet.3
4	xml.supportpuppet.4
5	xml.supportpuppet.5
6	xml.supportpuppet.6
7	xml.supportpuppet.7
8	xml.supportpuppet.8
9	xml.supportpuppet.9
10	xml.supportpuppet.10
11	xml.supportpuppet.11
12	xml.supportpuppet.12
13	xml.supportpuppet.13
14	xml.supportpuppet.14
15	xml.supportpuppet.15
16	xml.supportpuppet.16
17	xml.supportpuppet.17
18	xml.supportpuppet.18
19	xml.supportpuppet.19
20	xml.supportpuppet.20
21	xml.supportpuppet.21
22	xml.supportpuppet.22
23	xml.supportpuppet.23
24	xml.supportpuppet.24
25	xml.supportpuppet.25
26	xml.supportpuppet.26
27	xml.supportpuppet.27
28	xml.supportpuppet.28
29	xml.supportpuppet.29
30	xml.supportpuppet.30
31	xml.supportpuppet.31
32	xml.supportpuppet.32
33	xml.supportpuppet.33
34	xml.supportpuppet.34
35	xml.supportpuppet.35
36	xml.supportpuppet.36
37	xml.supportpuppet.37
38	xml.supportpuppet.38
39	xml.supportpuppet.39
40	xml.supportpuppet.40
41	xml.supportpuppet.41
42	xml.supportpuppet.42
43	xml.supportpuppet.43
44	xml.supportpuppet.44
45	xml.supportpuppet.45
46	xml.supportpuppet.46
47	xml.supportpuppet.47
48	xml.supportpuppet.48
49	xml.supportpuppet.49
50	xml.supportpuppet.50
51	xml.supportpuppet.51
52	xml.supportpuppet.52
53	xml.supportpuppet.53
54	xml.supportpuppet.54
55	xml.supportpuppet.55
56	xml.supportpuppet.56
57	xml.supportpuppet.57
58	xml.supportpuppet.58
59	xml.supportpuppet.59
60	xml.supportpuppet.60
61	xml.supportpuppet.61
62	xml.supportpuppet.62
63	xml.supportpuppet.63
64	xml.supportpuppet.64
65	xml.supportpuppet.65
66	xml.supportpuppet.66
67	xml.supportpuppet.67
68	xml.supportpuppet.68
69	xml.supportpuppet.69
70	xml.supportpuppet.70
71	xml.supportpuppet.71
72	xml.supportpuppet.72
73	xml.supportpuppet.73
74	xml.supportpuppet.74
75	xml.supportpuppet.75
76	xml.supportpuppet.76
77	xml.supportpuppet.77
78	xml.supportpuppet.78
79	xml.supportpuppet.79
80	xml.supportpuppet.80
81	xml.supportpuppet.81
82	xml.supportpuppet.82
83	xml.supportpuppet.83
84	xml.supportpuppet.84
85	xml.supportpuppet.85
86	xml.supportpuppet.86
87	xml.supportpuppet.87
88	xml.supportpuppet.88
89	xml.supportpuppet.89
90	xml.supportpuppet.90
91	xml.supportpuppet.91
92	xml.supportpuppet.92
93	xml.supportpuppet.93
94	xml.supportpuppet.94
95	xml.supportpuppet.95
96	xml.supportpuppet.96
97	xml.supportpuppet.97
98	xml.supportpuppet.98
99	xml.supportpuppet.99
100	xml.supportpuppet.100
101	xml.supportpuppet.101
102	xml.supportpuppet.102
103	xml.supportpuppet.103
104	xml.supportpuppet.104
105	xml.supportpuppet.105
106	xml.supportpuppet.106
107	xml.supportpuppet.107
108	xml.supportpuppet.108
109	xml.supportpuppet.109
110	xml.supportpuppet.110
111	xml.supportpuppet.111
112	xml.supportpuppet.112
113	xml.supportpuppet.113
114	xml.supportpuppet.114
115	xml.supportpuppet.115
116	xml.supportpuppet.116
117	xml.supportpuppet.117
118	xml.supportpuppet.118
119	xml.supportpuppet.119
120	xml.supportpuppet.120
121	xml.supportpuppet.121
122	xml.supportpuppet.122
123	xml.supportpuppet.123
124	xml.supportpuppet.124
125	xml.supportpuppet.125
126	xml.supportpuppet.126
127	xml.supportpuppet.127
128	xml.supportpuppet.128
129	xml.supportpuppet.129
130	xml.supportpuppet.130
131	xml.supportpuppet.131
132	xml.supportpuppet.132
133	xml.supportpuppet.133
134	xml.supportpuppet.134
135	xml.supportpuppet.135
136	xml.supportpuppet.136
137	xml.supportpuppet.137
138	xml.supportpuppet.138
139	xml.supportpuppet.139
140	xml.supportpuppet.140
141	xml.supportpuppet.141
142	xml.supportpuppet.142
143	xml.supportpuppet.143
144	xml.supportpuppet.144
145	xml.supportpuppet.145
146	xml.supportpuppet.146
147	xml.supportpuppet.147
148	xml.supportpuppet.148
149	xml.supportpuppet.149
150	xml.supportpuppet.150
151	xml.supportpuppet.151
152	xml.supportpuppet.152
153	xml.supportpuppet.153
154	xml.supportpuppet.154
155	xml.supportpuppet.155
156	xml.supportpuppet.156
157	xml.supportpuppet.157
158	xml.supportpuppet.158
159	xml.supportpuppet.159
160	xml.supportpuppet.160
161	xml.supportpuppet.161
162	xml.supportpuppet.162
163	xml.supportpuppet.163
164	xml.supportpuppet.164
165	xml.supportpuppet.165
166	xml.supportpuppet.166
167	xml.supportpuppet.167
168	xml.supportpuppet.168
169	xml.supportpuppet.169
170	xml.supportpuppet.170
171	xml.supportpuppet.171
172	xml.supportpuppet.172
173	xml.supportpuppet.173
174	0: Ask.\nAre you my master?
175	3: Servant Saber, the colonel according to the summon.\nMaster, give directions!
176	0: From now on, my black is with you,\nYour fate is with me.
177	1: You are not a regular master.\nBut you are my master.
178	1: I was taking a break.\nAt least I was thinking of keeping myself in perfect condition.
179	2: Our servant is a spirit.\nSo, revealing your identity will reveal your weaknesses.
180	2: Okay. If the Master says so...
181	2:Master.\nDid you promise to return before the day is over?
182	0: I have a suggestion.\nNow you have to gain experience in practice.
183	2: Colonel by summon.\nMaster, what's the situation?
184	0: In order not to repeat the same mistakes as last time,\nI will sleep in the master's room.\nYou have no complaints?
185	0:I don't have any problems.\nIs the master better than that?
186	1: Master, how are you feeling?
187	1: It looks like a good night's sleep.
188	1: If you wish, I will follow it.\nBecause I swore that this body will be your shield.\nI'll watch the end of the road to the end.
189	0:I accept the oath under the saber's name...\nI admit you as my master.
190	1: I am always at the master's side.
191	1: Master, the weather is very good today.
192	1: Would you like to play with me next time?
193	0: I think it's very important as a knight to not lose your pride.
194	0: Master, do you think it's time to eat?
195	0:I swear I will protect the Master and become a sword.\nEven if the contract disappears,\nthis oath will not change.
196	0: What happened, Master?
197	0: When deciding what is important,\nThank you in advance for consultation.
198	1: From now on, you need to gain experience in a practical way.
199	0: The previous master seemed to lose some concentration, but...
200	0: Master, don't overdo it.
201	1:Foot... Ah, no.\nI was hoping that the master was talking about someone else\nIt's a big deal.
202	1: Really, the master is unknown.
203	1: The master is also very talented.\nYou'll be able to compete with spirits.
204	1: You look tired.\nThe master needs a little rest.\nI'll clean up the back.
205	0:Bogu is a servant's hidden card.\nBut it requires a lot of magic to activate.
206	0:There may be an accident.\nIt's dangerous to go outside the master alone.
207	2: The desire to look younger than it really is is \nsome reason?
208	0:If you don't skip training every day,\nI think you can keep a healthy body even if you don't depend on drugs...
209	1: I don't snor, but...\nIt would be okay for the master to consider it once.
210	1: I would like a village to buy at a good price.
211	1: Then Master, let's go.
212	0: I will escort you to the village.
213	1: Master, I will be with you.
214	0: Where is this destination?
215	1: I would like a village to buy at a good price.
216	1: Then Master, let's go.
217	0: I will escort you to the village.
218	1: Master, I will be with you.
219	0: Where is this destination?
220	1: I don't know about ore...\nI think I can make a good sword with this ore.
221	1: Then Master, let's go.
222	0: I will escort you to the village.
223	2: This sweet smell...\nIs it from that load?
224	1: It smells good.\nIt is a fragrance that stimulates appetite.
225	1: Ho. Is it pasta.\nYes, it's interesting.
226	1: I haven't thought about using bears for food, but...\nI would like to try it once I have the opportunity.
227	0: I will escort you to the village.
228	1: Master, I will be with you.
229	0: Where is this destination?
230	1: I would like a village to buy at a good price.
231	1: Then Master, let's go.
232	0: As for me who has walked the road as a knight, it's a very unrelated thing.
233	1: Master, I will be with you.
234	0: Where is this destination?
235	1: I would like a village to buy at a good price.
236	1: Then Master, let's go.
237	0: I will escort you to the village.
238	1: Master, I will be with you.
239	0: Where is this destination?
240	1: I would like a village to buy at a good price.
241	1: Then Master, let's go.
242	0: I will escort you to the village.
243	2: This doesn't look like an ordinary sword.\nI feel something dark.
244	0: Where is this destination?
245	1: It's a great thing.
246	1: Then Master, let's go.
247	1: Tyr Cornale credit level 1 is here, cheer up!
248	1: Tyr Conale credit level is already 6!
249	1: Dunbarton's credit level has become 4.
250	1: Dunbarton has reached credit level 9!\nMaster, you were in trouble.
251	1: Vanhor credit level is 5!
252	1: Vanhor credit level 9!\nMaster, you've had a lot of trouble.
253	1:Imen Maha is credit level 1.\nYou just have to work hard!
254	1: Emen Mach credit level 8!
255	1: Taltin credit level has already reached level 5! Try a little more!
256	1: Taltin credit level is 7!
257	1:Tara's credit level has been 2!\nI think it will be level 3 with a little more.
258	1: You have achieved Tara Credit Level 6!
259	1: Carb credit level 3! Try a little harder!
260	1: Carb's credit level has reached level 8!
261	1:Belbust credit level is 4
262	1:Belbust credit level has already reached 9!
263	0: Then, shall we go to the next place?
264	0: Master, aren't you heavy?
265	1: If you think that this is also one of your disciplines, you will feel more energetic than \n.
266	1: Master, cheer up!
267	0: Then, shall we go to the next place?
268	0: Master, aren't you heavy?
269	1: If you think that this is also one of your disciplines, you will feel more energetic than \n.
270	1: Master, cheer up!
271	0: Then, shall we go to the next place?
272	1: An excellent horse is said to choose the owner.\nA horse is a clever animal.
273	1: I often remember running on horseback with several knights.
274	2: It's my first time seeing an elephant directly,\nbut it's a smarter animal than it looks.
275	2: Again, the elephant is so strong that it is so big.\nYou can carry so much load at once...
276	2: Although it's not as easy as it sounds,\nthe elephant was a very fast animal.
277	1: It's different from the lion's dignity,\nthe elephant is quite imposing.
278	2: I can feel the remnants of magic.
279	2: Master, the situation outside...
280	2: Master, I can feel the pillage.\nPlease be careful!
281	1: There is a sense of incongruity that is used for nerves,\nbut there seems to be no danger.
282	1: The threat of looting seems to have passed.\nYou can now rest assured.
283	1: You seem to have avoided unnecessary fights.\nMaster, keep going.
284	3: If you don't come from that side, I go!
285	3: The enemy is the calculation that ends here, Master!
286	3:Master, behind me!\n I'll take care of this!
287	3: Stop.\nIf you go further, you will have to be prepared!
288	3: Be careful, Master!
289	3: Master, watch your back!
290	3: Servant Saber,\nI will fight as a master sword!
291	3: You can't even touch the master!
292	1: You are also my master!
293	1: Now, let's go again.
294	1: This little enemy is not the master and my opponent.
295	4:{0}{taken}...\n... Ugh, yum...
296	4:{0}{taken}...\nI'm not satisfied, Master...
297	4:{0}{taken}.\nIt is my fault.
298	4:{0}{} have been taken away.\nI think we should borrow the bounty hunter's hand!
299	4: The stolen criminal who stole the trade item has already appeared on the bulletin board...\nI'm sorry.
300	4: You lost your trade...\nI won't lose it next time.
301	6: It's another outrageous partner.\nThis is no luck.
302	5: Ah, I definitely agree with that opinion.
303	6:Well, I'm very dissatisfied...\nI admit you as a master.
304	5: In form, I'll follow you.\nBut I'm fighting myself.
305	6: Um, have you made me angry? No, of course I respect your position.\nI was called to win the Master.
306	5: My victory is yours, and I'll give you everything I get in the fight.\nYou won't have any complaints?
307	6: Well, leave the work behind to me, and you only think about your own safety.\nI don't want anything from you.
308	5:...Yes.\nYour personality is largely understood, Master.
309	6: Now I feel a strong force on your words.\n...It's a difficult thing.
310	6: You must be first class.
311	5: I'll regret the rant right now.\nI won't accept it until then.
312	5:...I can't tell you who I am.\nBecause I don't know.
313	6:I'm the servant you called.\nMight not be the strongest?
314	6: The sun is already in the middle.\nYou can't hit it.
315	6: You are...\nYou are weak in the morning, really.
316	5: Are you going back now, Master?
317	5: Servant wants to help human beings deeply in his heart,\nDo you really believe that?
318	5:A spirit is just a device.\nIf something bad happens, it's called out,\nand it just disappears after processing it.
319	5:A scavenger who is deprived of his will and works for humans forever.\nThat's a convenient thing called a spirit... guardian.
320	5: It's just hypocrisy to fight for someone other than yourself.
321	5: What you want is not victory, but peace.\nThere's nothing like this in the world.
322	5: How long will you be playing?
323	6:...I can't.\nIt's your job to cover when the owner isn't in my condition.\nI'll keep watching until you find my condition.
324	5: If you're fighting with your own will,\nthese sins and punishments were created by yourself.\nIt's even more of a burden to carry it.
325	5: You need a reason to fight. But that shouldn't be strange.\nIf you fight for more than that, there's only one you can get.\nThere's no way to save people.
326	5: Being a bright person means someone who is more dazzling than others.\nThere's no such thing as a time when you have to bite it...\nAnd you must be that kind of person.
327	5: I told you one day. I have no pride as a hero.\nOf course. All I have is a stupid regret.\nI mean. Heroes shouldn't have been.
328	5: I'm not the only one who became a hero with my own light.\nBecause I'm just a guardian who sold myself after death and became a hero.
329	5: Has the Master ever thought about your own definition?
330	6: This is anxiety and wants...\nI can't take my eyes off the master.
331	6:I'm a servant summoned for battle,\nI hope you're not a deacon who cares for you\ndon't forget.
332	6:I trust in your skills and judgment,\nI would appreciate it if you don't make any mistakes in important places.
333	5: I usually suppress the consumption of magical power by making it spiritual.\nNo matter how much you are, you don't have unlimited power, right?
334	5: Then shall we start, Master?
335	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
336	5: Is this your next destination?
337	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
338	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
339	5: Then shall we start, Master?
340	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
341	5: Is this your next destination?
342	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
343	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
344	5: Then shall we start, Master?
345	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
346	5: Is this your next destination?
347	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
348	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
349	5: Then shall we start, Master?
350	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
351	5: Is this your next destination?
352	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
353	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
354	5: Then shall we start, Master?
355	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
356	5: Is this your next destination?
357	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
358	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
359	5: Then shall we start, Master?
360	6: Next, let's have a cup of black tea.\nIf you drink it at a table like this, it will taste better.
361	5: Is this your next destination?
362	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
363	6: If you have a good drink to fill this wine rack
364	5: Then shall we start, Master?
365	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
366	5: Is this your next destination?
367	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
368	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
369	5: Then shall we start, Master?
370	6: Let me take the lead.\nLet me come and stick behind you.
371	5: Is this your next destination?
372	6: Oh my god...\nI can't help it, I'll be there too.
373	6: I'll keep the back.\nIt's good to be safe and lead the way.\nShall we start?
374	6:Tir Conale credit level 1, try a little bit more.
375	6: Tyr Cornell's credit level has already reached 6.
376	6: Dunbarton's credit level has been 4.\nIf you add a little more, can you reach level 5?
377	6: Dunbarton has reached credit level 9.\nGood job, Master.
378	6: Vanhor credit level is 5.
379	6: It's Vanhor credit level 9.\nGood job, Master.
380	6: Emen Maha credit level 1 level.\nTry a little harder.
381	6: Emen Mach credit level 8.
382	6: Taltin's credit level has already reached level 5. How long do you think is left?
383	6: Taltin's credit level is 7!
384	6: Tara's credit level has become 2.
385	6: Tara achieved credit level 6.
386	6:Carb credit level 3. Try a little more.
387	6:Carb's credit level has reached level 8.
388	6:Belbust credit level is 4.\nTry a little more.
389	6:Belbust credit level has already reached 9!
390	6: Anyway, you're buying useless hardship, you.
391	5: Is this your next destination?
392	6: Sometimes this is not bad either.
393	6: If you're my master, this would be a good thing.
394	5: Why don't you consider a more convenient means of transportation next time?
395	5: Is this your next destination?
396	6: Sometimes this is not bad either.
397	6: If you're my master, this would be a good thing.
398	5: Is this your next destination?
399	6: Sometimes this is not bad either.
400	5: Carriage...\nIt's a classic but quite effective vehicle.
401	6: How to tame an elephant and use it as a transportation...\nI don't know who it is, but I thought so.
402	5: Is this your next destination?
403	6: Sometimes this is not bad either.
404	5: Elephant...\nA big, strong animal.
405	7: I saw it again.\nYou look like you're living.
406	7: Master, I can feel the enemy.\nBe careful.
407	7:You can see your eyes nearby.\nSomeone is watching.
408	6: The enemy seems to have gone away.\nIt will be safe for the time being.
409	6: The response of the looting group has disappeared.\nIt's okay if you don't care anymore.
410	6: Okay, now it seems safe.\nLet's hurry up the road.
411	8:I won't let it go.\nI have to overcome it someday.
412	8: How many enemies?\nThis is not a handicap when considering the power difference.
413	8: Turn off!!
414	8:I am the bone of my sword.\nUnknown to Death. Nor known to Life.\nUnlimited blade works!
415	8: Do you think you can get this much!
416	8: Master, leave it here!
417	8: Master's attack power is low,\ndon't forget!
418	8:It's an enemy.\nTake care of it here!
419	6:Great.\nBut that's not enough.
420	6: Excuse me.\nI thought I'd fall early, but I was surprisingly persistent.
421	6: I think it's cleared up.\nSo let's start again.
422	9: Sorry, {0}{there} was stolen.\nIt was a very careful enemy.
423	9:{0}{taken}...\nAnd my defeat.
424	9:{0}{taken}...\nYou have made this mistake...!
425	9:Why don't you lend a bounty hunter's hand to find the lost trade?
426	9: The killer who stole the traded goods\n Looks like he's already on the bulletin board...
427	9: The sooner a phenomenon is caught, the more stolen items can be recovered.
428	14:...What, really...\nBecause I didn't sleep until late yesterday, just a little more...
429	10: I'm actually a little sleepy, me.
430	12:...Hung, I know you don't have to.
431	10: I'll check,\nYou're my partner, right?
432	12: What are you doing?\nDo you know me as a fool?
433	11:Hey~ The head turns faster than it looks.\nYes, it's fun, it's fun.
434	10: This is the magic decision passed on to our family.\nIf it is a carved magic here, it can be activated by injecting magical power.
435	10: I mean, the chance in front of you is an attention not to be missed.
436	12: What?\n What, what? Staring at the person's face...
437	11: I'm kinda talking...\nWould you like to take a break?
438	11: I'm not really giving you power.\nBut I'll help you unless you betray me.
439	10:I can accumulate simple forces, change the flow,\nconvert and preserve the power of various objects.
440	10:Hey, what if.\nIf you have a child who enters another's house as a stepdaughter, regardless of her doctor,\nHow will she grow up?
441	10:Magic practice?\nI never thought it was difficult.\nIt was fun to learn new things.
442	11:I'm basically a hedonist.\nIt's a duty to follow my father,\nbut I don't do that unless it's fun.
443	11: Cooperating with you is because you have fun.
444	14: Ooh... Sorry, wait...\nI think it'll take a little more...\nMy new...
445	11: Let's go out today. Come on and get ready.\nWhat are you doing, of course you're going to play.\nDate, date.
446	11: Come on! Where to start~\nWhere are your requests?
447	12: Ha, I'm doing...\nPush up before going to bed...\nWhy not?
448	11: Ah, there's a sauce on my mouth.\nWould you like to clean it?
449	12: No! I'm mistaken...\nI'm not really concerned about you...
450	10:...Hey, if it was fun, honestly say yes.\nExcuse me for escorting here.
451	10:...Hey, have you ever regretted what you did?\n...I don't want to go as far as possible.\nBut it will be difficult. Probably, more than I think.
452	12: You, you!\nIf you put the words that came to your mind without thinking,\nit's a misunderstanding somewhere!
453	12: Well, if I leave something like you alone, I can't sleep because I'm anxious...\nTo borrow your words, I don't hate you either.\nI mean, even if I'm with you, there's no problem, actually.
454	10: Heung, what do I think about this?\nYou know what I'm doing?
455	11: The weather is really good today.\nWould you like to go out to play?
456	11:Aha, I'm awful. I'm awful!\nYou like it because you have a tingle on your face right away.
457	10: Huh? Ah~ Yes, you were aware.\nIsn't it necessary to worry, though?\nYou still have no problem.
458	10: How about this?\nDoes it taste good?
459	11: Oops, did I make fun of you?\nBecause it responds as expected,\nIt's just fun.
460	11:You look good.\nIs it okay now?\nGood thing~
461	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
462	12: Me, I don't really need this.
463	12: Me, I don't really need this.
464	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
465	12: Me, I don't really need this.
466	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
467	10: Which town is your next destination?
468	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
469	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
470	12: Wow, bold...\nI think it's difficult to digest?
471	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
472	10: Which town is your next destination?
473	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
474	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
475	10: You know what?\nOriginally, alchemy was a study to turn lead into gold.
476	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
477	10: Which town is your next destination?
478	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
479	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
480	10:Is this a little strange?\nThere are many things in the world.
481	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
482	10: Which town is your next destination?
483	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
484	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
485	10:Is this a little strange?\nThere are many things in the world.
486	11: Oh, is this a little like what I have?
487	10:Sometimes when my head is complicated,\nI sometimes feel like drinking a cup of tea.
488	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
489	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
490	10: There were a lot of these in the basement of my house...\I didn't have anything to write about.
491	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
492	10: Which town is your next destination?
493	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
494	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
495	10:Is this a little strange?\nThere are many things in the world.
496	10: Some people are looking for a product like this.
497	10: Which town is your next destination?
498	11: Since it's hard, I'd like to sell it for a good price.
499	11: I wish I could find a village that would sell expensive.
500	10:Is this a little strange?\nThere are many things in the world.
501	11: Tyr Conale credit level 1, cheer up!
502	11: Tyr Conale credit level is already 6!
503	11: Dunbarton Credit Level 4!\nIf you add a little more, you can become Level 5.
504	11: Dunbarton achieved credit level 9!\nIt took a long time~
505	11: Vanhor credit level is already 5!
506	11: Banhor credit level 9 achieved!
507	11: Emen Maha credit level 1 level.\nStrive a little!
508	11: Emen Mach credit level 8 achieved!
509	11: It seemed to be a long time ago, but Taltin's credit level is already 5! Try a little more!
510	11: Hua~ Taltin's credit level is 7.
511	11: Tara Credit Level 2!\nIf you add a little more, you can become Level 3.
512	11: Tara achieved credit level 6!
513	11: It's Carb Level 3. Go a little harder!
514	11:Carb's credit level has reached level 8!
515	11:Belbust credit level is 4.\nStrive a little more!
516	11:Hey~ Have you already reached the Belbust credit level of 9?
517	11: Come on, let's go!
518	10:After...\nPreparation OK, time OK, wavelength good.
519	11: Does that look heavy?\nYes? You seem to be having fun, you won't be at all♪
520	10: Which way are you going this time?
521	11: Come on, let's go!
522	10:After...\nPreparation OK, time OK, wavelength good.
523	11: Does that look heavy?\nYes? You seem to be having fun, you won't be at all♪
524	10: Which way are you going this time?
525	11: Come on, let's go!
526	10: It is not a very comfortable ride...\nBut the carriage is fast~.
527	11: Which way are you going this time?
528	11: Come on, let's go!
529	10: Wow...\nIt's a new story, but the elephant is really big.
530	10: Didn't you know there was an opportunity to ride an elephant that you only saw at the zoo?
531	10: Which way are you going this time?
532	12: It hasn't begun yet,\nbut there's nothing bad about it.
533	12: The lord is reacting...\nThere must be someone watching around.
534	12: Quiet. If it acts loud, it's undetectable.
535	11: Whoo... I think the danger is out of the way.\Can I let go of my heart for the time being?
536	11:Hugh... I'm a little nervous.\nNow it's okay. Come on, let's go!
537	11: The pillage has disappeared.\nSo shall we go lively again?
538	13: I won't interrupt!\nYour power, show me here!
539	13: I'm relieved. I don't say anything without odds.\nLeave it to me.
540	13: What can I do about this?\nThese magicians are self-defense...\nThis is a required course!
541	13: Predators are aiming for a trade!\nWould you like that?
542	13: I'll take this over!\nYou keep the trade!
543	13: I'm sorry, but I'll take care of it here.\nIf you hang around in front of me like this...\nMy nerves won't stand!
544	13: Don't move if you don't want to be sick.\nThen I'll make you comfortable soon.\nIf you get wrong with something strange, you die!
545	13: Don't run away with him!\nIf the target keeps moving...\nI'll do it sincerely!
546	11: You are cool. It was surprising.
547	11: Are you pretty?\nI saw it again.
548	11: This is natural for Rin Osaka.
549	14:{0}{taken}...\nLin, this is your responsibility...
550	14:{0}{taken}...\nYou can't go back empty-handed like this?\nYou have to make up for the failure.
551	14:{0}{taken}...\nBut I never give up.\nI will not forgive you if I apologize because it's time to knock down the predators and get back the trade!
552	14: This is...\nAnyone's hands on my trade!
553	14: I did it again...\nI can't help doing it... Ah~!
554	14: Ah, really inflexible guy...
555	15: Hi, brother.
556	15: Hello, sister.
557	15: Hi. I'm Iri.\nI'm Iriyaspil von Einzbern.
558	15: Drive the rabbit to the end,\nand kill it when you're scared.
559	16: Huh, huh, huh, it's caught ♪\My brother is really fun.\nIs it like that when you hit me, it sounds like this
560	16: Huh, huh, huh, it's caught ♪\My sister is really fun.\nIs it like that when I hit it, it sounds like it's ringing?
561	15: I'm back...!\nCome on, brother!
562	15: I'm back...!\nCome on, sister!
563	18: Magic? Human salvation?\nOnly humans can be happy with it.\nWhat makes us alive?
564	15: Ah... Yeah.\nYou've been there, brother.
565	15: Ah... Yeah.\nYou've been there, sister.
566	15: If I do this, I can rest assured.\nBecause I always protected me.
567	15: The castle of Einzbern where I was staying is pretty boring.
568	16: I was looking forward to meeting my brother.
569	16: I was looking forward to meeting my sister.
570	17: What are the Homuncruises alive for?\nYes, nothing.
571	15: Is my name difficult?\nYou can just call it Iriya.
572	16:My brother is also fun.
573	16: Sister is fun too.
574	15: What are Sarah and Liz doing by now?
575	18: It's okay, you can live alone...\nIt's okay, even alone...
576	18: I don't know. It has nothing to do with me.\nI decided to live alone.
577	15:Your brother was protecting me.\nYou were protecting me.\nYour brother is so strong...
578	15:My sister was willing to protect me.\nYou were protecting me.\nYou are very strong...
579	16: Let's play together, brother.
580	16: Let's play together, sister.
581	16:My magic, would you like to see it?\nWell~ I'll show you next time.
582	15: This is the Holy Grail War?\nYou know I'm going to win, right?
583	16: Now... what are you going to do today, brother?
584	16: Now... what are you going to play with today, sister?
585	16: My servant Berserker is the strongest in the world!\nBecause he's stronger than your brother?
586	16: My Servant Berserker is the strongest in the world!\nBecause she is stronger than her sister?
587	16: Hmm~ where are you going to take me today?
588	15: This doesn't really work for me?
589	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
590	15: I don't need this.
591	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
592	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
593	15: Um... Who likes this?
594	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
595	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
596	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
597	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
598	15: Um... Who likes this?
599	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
600	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
601	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
602	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
603	15: Um... Who likes this?
604	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
605	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
606	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
607	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
608	15: Um... Who likes this?
609	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
610	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
611	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
612	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
613	15: Ah, your mother had something similar.\nIt was bigger and more colorful than this.
614	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
615	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
616	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
617	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
618	15: Um... Who likes this?
619	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
620	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
621	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
622	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
623	15: Um... Who likes this?
624	16: Ah, I've seen this in Einzbern Castle.
625	15: I wish I could sell it expensive.
626	15: Have you seen this for the first time?\nWhich town are you going to take?
627	16:Where... this looks a little strange.
628	16: Tyr Cornale's credit level 1, cheer up!
629	16:Tir Cornell's credit level is already 6!
630	16: Dunbarton Credit Level 4!\nIf you add a little more, you can be level 5.
631	16: Dunbarton achieved credit level 9!\nOh~ it was too long~
632	16: Vanhor credit level is already 5!
633	16: Achieved Banhor Credit Level 9!
634	16: Emen Maha credit level 1 level.\nGive a little bit!
635	16: Amen Mach credit level 8 achieved!
636	16: It seemed to be a long time ago, but Taltin's credit level is already 5! Try a little more!
637	16: Wow~ Taltin's credit level is 7.
638	16:Tara Credit Level 2!\nYou can become Level 3 with just a little more.
639	16:Tara achieved credit level 6!
640	16:Carb Level 3! Go a little harder!
641	16:Carb's credit level has reached level 8!
642	16:Belbust credit level is 4.\nPlease try a little harder!
643	16: Wow~ Belbust's credit level has already reached 9!
644	16: Brother, this is it!
645	16: Sister, this is it!
646	15: Hmm~ Are you so hard at that?
647	16: Should I go all the way?
648	16: Brother, this is it!
649	16: Sister, this is it!
650	15: Hmm~ Are you so hard at that?
651	16: Should I go all the way?
652	16: Brother, this is it!
653	16: Sister, this is it!
654	15: The carriage is quite fast.\nOf course not as much as Berserker.
655	16: Brother, this is it!
656	16: Sister, this is it!
657	15: Wow, this is an elephant.\nIt's really big. I think it's bigger than our Berserker?
658	16:Elephants look pretty strong.\nMaybe not as much as our Berserkers.
659	18: I have a suspicious feeling nearby.\nMy brother, it's good to be careful.
660	18: I have a suspicious feeling nearby.\nI like to be careful.
661	18: Uh yeah... I think a looting party is staring nearby?\nWhat are you going to do? Do you want to avoid it?\nOr... will you get rid of it?
662	16:Yeah, I think it's okay now.\nI don't feel anything at all.
663	16: You wouldn't have to have avoided it...\nWell, it's good to have less annoying things.
664	16: I think it would be safe enough.\nSo shall we continue?
665	18: Is the consultation over?\nSo, can I start?
666	18: Then I'll kill you.\nGet hurt!
667	18:Hey, be scared.\nYou're attacking without a word, it's like a beast.
668	18: Are you trying to stick to the front?\nI'm brave but I'm stupid.
669	18:You can't lose anyone.\nYou are the strongest in the world!
670	18: My sister won't lose anyone.\nI'm the strongest in the world!
671	18:...don't lose, brother!!
672	18:...Don't lose, Sister!!
673	18: Get it done, brother!
674	18: Get hurt, sister!
675	18: The predator has attacked!
676	16: Hmm~ I saw it again, brother.\nIt's quite right?
677	16: Hmm~ I saw it again, sister.\nIt's quite right?
678	16: Heung~ Those guys aren't good enough.
679	16: Then shall we leave again?
680	17:{0}{Lost}...\n...Lies... Lies, it's a lie.\nIt must be a lie!
681	17: Ah, {0}{l} was stolen...\nNo, I hate you, brother...
682	17: Ah, {0}{l} was stolen...\nNo, I hate you, sister...
683	17:쳇...I lost {0}{}...\nI won't let you go next time!
684	17: A killer who stole a trade item has already appeared on the bulletin board...\nI can't forgive!
685	17: I hope that Hyun-bum is caught quickly...
686	yui
687	saber
688	archer
689	rin
690	illyasviel
691	Saber
692	Archer
693	Rin
694	Illyasviel
695	tuto_guide
