0	Makes you rich.\nThe Ducati's baggage is like a Meteor.
1	I want to stand on the theater stage.\nI must play the part.\nI know the feeling.
2	The butler is neglected by me. I want to eat milk and fish.
3	It's been 29 years since I haven't been in love...\nI've been able to write magic if I'm solo for 30 years, but I'm going to break the world next year!!!!\n...So, let's do a romance this year.
4	First degree health, second degree health, stamina is the national power.\nPlease always keep all of us healthy.
5	It's been 9 years already. Even after 10 years and 20 years, we will be together.
6	I want to be alone. Please log out all.
7	제발 헉..헉.. 하루만 헉..헉..헉.. 쉬었다가 헉..헉..헉.. 일 했으면 헉..헉.. 좋겠네요 헉..헉..헉..헉..
8	I wish I had a day when three people could laugh together.
9	You want to hear my wishes? Then give me the money.
10	Look at this guy
11	It's getting more and more to miss the hammer from the fortress..\nI've devoted my whole life to blacksmithing, but now I want my hands to slip less.
12	Stay healthy for a long time Grandma.
13	Please make your diet successful.\nI want to lose weight.\nHow to lose weight... Oh, I'll come back after eating some chicken
14	This note was first launched in Dunbarton and gave good luck to the recipient.\nThis note, which has been transferred to you now, must leave you within 4 seconds.\nYou need to send 30 copies, including this note, to anyone in need. To do.
15	Detailed description is omitted.
